<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hengli Moments · Power Frontier on Henli | Energy</title>
    <link>https://xinnenglifang.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hengli Moments · Power Frontier on Henli | Energy</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 11:07:10 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://xinnenglifang.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Customer Case: Cracking the “Last-Three-Kilometre” Efficiency Code</title>
      <link>https://xinnenglifang.com/blog/blog-post-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 11:07:10 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://xinnenglifang.com/blog/blog-post-4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Client&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;code&gt;Hutong Express Supply Chain (Shanghai) Co., Ltd.&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;Industry:&lt;/strong&gt; Urban supply-chain distribution, community retail / pharma instant-delivery provider&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;Application Scenario:&lt;/strong&gt; High-frequency, small-batch deliveries in city cores’ “last three kilometres” (using small electric tricycles and micro electric vans)&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;Cooperation Period:&lt;/strong&gt; June 2023 – present&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;Products in Use:&lt;/strong&gt; Hengli New Energy high-energy-density, long-life Lithium Iron Phosphate (LFP) battery packs&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Company Named Core Supplier to an Industry Giant</title>
      <link>https://xinnenglifang.com/blog/blog-post-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 11:07:10 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://xinnenglifang.com/blog/blog-post-3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After years of deep cultivation in the new-energy power sector, we have reached another major milestone today: thanks to our leading technology and outstanding product quality, the company has secured a significant strategic order from Jeboo Power and has officially become its core lithium-battery supplier. This in-depth cooperation not only demonstrates strong market recognition of our solutions but also elevates our overall competitiveness in the power-lithium field to a new level.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Company Embarks on Robust Overseas Market Strategy</title>
      <link>https://xinnenglifang.com/blog/blog-post-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 11:07:10 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://xinnenglifang.com/blog/blog-post-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After firmly establishing a leading position in China’s new-energy power-battery market, the company is officially sounding the horn for its global expansion. Backed by strong technological prowess, outstanding product quality, and large-scale manufacturing advantages, we are poised to bring safe, efficient, and reliable lithium solutions to a broader international stage and take an active role in the worldwide transition to green energy.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another Breakthrough in Our Core Technology R&amp;D</title>
      <link>https://xinnenglifang.com/blog/blog-post-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 11:07:10 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://xinnenglifang.com/blog/blog-post-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Amid rapid iterations in battery technology, our R&amp;amp;D center has delivered yet another inspiring achievement. Leveraging robust in-house innovation and forward-looking technical roadmaps, we have made major advances in core material systems, cell architecture, and system integration. The result is a significant boost in overall product performance, further strengthening our leadership in the power-lithium sector. This milestone elevates our R&amp;amp;D capabilities to a new level and provides strong support for meeting global demand for high-performance, safe, long-life lithium batteries.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
